Chui Wing Sze, Sherry

Flat E, 17/F, Block 5, Phase 2 Belvedere Garden, 620 Castle Peak Road, Tsuen Wan, N.T., Hong Kong Tel: 9744-2082 Email: sherrycws@gmail.com

Personal Summary

A graduate at the University of Hong Kong. Responsible, detail-oriented, proactive and able to work under pressure. Effectively work in a multi-task and team environment. Have good organizational skill and specialize in accounting & administrative work. Fluent in Chinese, English and Mandarin. Proficiency in computer applications. Good commands of English and Chinese character inputs and Microsoft Office Suite.

Working experience

1/11/2012 - 31/3/2017 Senior Accounting Officer - Small business management (Promoted from Accounting Officer on 1 Jan 2016)

Full-time position in Lynks C.P.A. Limited

- · Handling full sets of accounts for clients
- Preparing monthly consolidated management reports & performance variance report
- Preparing daily payments
- Preparing monthly salary charts and calculating China tax
- Preparing and completing Employer's Return of Remuneration & Pension submitting to IRD

4/7/2011 - 12/9/2012 Staff Accountant 2 (Promoted from Staff Accountant 1 on 1 Apr 2012)

Full-time position in Lak & Associates C.P.A. Limited

Planning and performing audit assignments

7/7/2010 - 14/4/2011 Administrative Officer

Full-time position in China.hk Intellectual Property Services Co., Ltd

- · Processing of trademark and design applications worldwide under the supervision of senior members of the company
- General office administration
- Sales & marketing administration

27/7/2009 - 26/8/2009 Financial planning assistant

Summer Internship in Winnie Tsui & Company which works for Manulife International Limited

- Compiling and categorizing data, documenting and verifying reasonableness
- Assisting in analysis of clients' personal financial situation, plans and objectives
- Participating in the development and analysis of financial strategies in clients' wealth management creation and protection.

Professional Memberships

Student member, Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA) (papers F1 - F9, P2 - P3 passed)

Public Certification

2017 Advanced Diploma in Accounting and Business, ACCA
 2009 Insurance Intermediaries Qualifying Examination, papers I & III

2007 Level 3 Certificate in Accounting, LCCI

Pass with Distinction

Education

2007-2010 One major in Risk Management and one major in Finance, Bachelor of Science, The University of Hong Kong

2005-2007 Liu Po Shan Memorial College

2000-2005 Ho Fung College

Result of Hong Kong Advanced Level Examination (HKALE)

Principles of Accounts B Pure Mathematics B
Use of English D Chinese Language and Culture D

References

Ms. Shirley Ng, the Director

Lynks C.P.A. Limited

Contact no: 2815-8218

Ms. Carrie Hui, the Director

Lak & Associates C.P.A. Limited

Contact no: 2526-5511

Available date: immediately available Present salary: HK\$25,000 Expected salary: HK\$26,000 (negotiable)